

# AHMED ABBASSI

#### **Software Engineering Student**

- @ a.abbassi21306@pi.tn
- **J** +216 23-631-633
- Tunis, Tunisia

- in ahmed-abbassi-
- 3ibsi69

#### **SKILLS**



JavaScript | Python

Microsoft Word | SQL

Microsoft Excel **PLSQL** 

LateX

Linux

## CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Word (office 2016)

Microsoft Excel (office 2016)

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a 21 years old student seeking opportunities to apply my knowledge and skills in a real-world setting, and eager to contribute to innovative projects that make a positive impact. I hope to bring the best out of myself and work within a well-communicated team.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Part-time Sales Associate | Decathlon

10/06/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | Karriery

= 29/05/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | B and smile

**1** 01/08/2022 - 31/08/2022

Tunis. Tunisia

# LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native

English: Intermediate / B2

French: Intermediate / B1

### Software Engineering | Polytech INTL

iii 09 2021 - Present

**EDUCATION** 

Tunis, Tunisia

Tunis, Tunisia

Computer Science Baccalaureate | Rue de Russie High School

# **PROJECTS**

**i** 09 2020 - 05 2021

### Portfolio Website (React) 😯

**21/06/2023 - 22/06/2023** 

HTML CSS SCSS React JavaScript

#### Portfolio Website 💭

- **1** 05/06/2023 08/06/2023
- HTML CSS SCSS JavaScript

#### Weather-app (7)

- **1**4/06/2023 14/06/2023
- HTML | CSS | SCSS | JavaScript

#### Stop Watch 🜎

- **1**3/06/2023 13/06/2023
- HTML | CSS | SCSS | JavaScript

# INTERESTS

Gaming

Music

Sports

# 

• C